makemoneyadultcontent.com 2017-05-26

# Privacy Policy - Make Money Adult content

At Makemoneyadultcontent.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Makemoneyadultcontent.com and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, Makemoneyadultcontent.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

Makemoneyadultcontent.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to send advertisements and links that appear on Makemoneyadultcontent.com directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Makemoneyadultcontent.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Makemoneyadultcontent.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser’s respective websites.

 **Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of Makemoneyadultcontent.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

We use Google Analytics to collect information about the use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they were visiting prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies in your browser.

Google Analytics employs cookies to define user sessions, which allows for the collection of data about how visitors are using the websites. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that specific website. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.

If you want, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser.

Cheers,   

You can always reach me at [Contact US](http://makemoneyadultcontent.com/contact-us/) or through **contact@makemoneyadultcontent.com** for any queries. I will be quick to reply.   
Join our FREE Private VIP [Facebook Group](https://www.facebook.com/groups/makemoneyadultcontent/)   
This single step (takes 5 minutes and baby easy) is helping me make more than $10,000/month. Thank god i did this 7 years back, cant imagine my life without it. Check it out for free: [Click Here](http://www.makemoneyadultcontent.com/hostgator-review-best-web-hosting-adult-porn-websites/)
